export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "What is the correct command to create a new React project ?",
        options:[ "npx create-react-app appname",
            "npm install create-react-app",
            "npx install create-react-app -g",
            "install - l create-react-app"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        options:["	Create","Extends","Inherits", "Delete"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run?",
        options: ["3OOO", "8080", "5000", "3030"],
        answer: 1
    },
    
    {
        question: "Which of the following valid component return type of React ?",
        options: ["2", "5", "1", "3"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        options: ["	State & Props", "Services & Components","State & Services Cross","State & Component"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
        options: ["SetinitialComponent","renderComponent","render","All of the above"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        options: [	"Compiler","Transpilar","Both of the above","None of the above"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        options: ["SetState","Render with arguments","Props","PropTypes"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
        options: ["this.State{}","this.setState","this.setChangeState","All the above" ],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
        options: ["self()","inherits()","this()","super()"],
        answer:4
    },
];